<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WeatherApp</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please Wait&#8230;</string>

    <string name="image_contentDescription">image</string>
    <string name="miles_per_hour">miles/hour</string>
    <string name="navigation_open">navigation_open</string>
    <string name="navigation_close">navigation_close</string>
    <string name="version">version\n</string>
    <string name="email">nehavns2848@gmail.com\n</string>
    <string name="subject_for_email">Report Bug - Weather APP</string>
    <string name="email_body">Email body</string>
    <string name="share_title">Shring the weather application\n</string>
    <string name="About_Content">Welcome to the Weather App, your go-to source for accurate and up-to-date weather forecasts tailored to your location. Whether you\'re planning your day, organizing outdoor activities, or simply staying informed, our app delivers comprehensive weather information to keep you prepared for any conditions. Our commitment to accuracy and reliability ensures that you receive timely updates on current weather conditions, hourly forecasts, and extended outlooks. With intuitive features and user-friendly interface, navigating through weather data has never been easier.</string>
    <string name="weather">Weather</string>
    <string name="degree">Degree</string>
    <string name="minimum">Minimum</string>
    <string name="wind">Wind</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="sunrise">Sunrise</string>
    <string name="sunset">Sunset</string>
    <string name="country">Country</string>
    <string name="maximum">Maximum</string>
    <string name="per_cent">per cent</string>
    <string name="condition">condition</string>
    <string name="privacy">At Weather Application, we are dedicated to safeguarding your privacy when you use our Weather Application. This Privacy Policy outlines how we collect, use, and protect your information. Collection of Information: Our Weather Application only requests access to your device\'s location. This information is solely used to retrieve weather data from the OpenWeather API. We do not collect any personal information such as your name, email address, or contact details. Use of Information: The location information obtained is exclusively utilized to provide you with accurate weather forecasts and updates within the Application. We do not employ this data for any other purpose, and we do not share it with third parties. Data Retention: We do not retain any personal information collected by the Application. The location data is used momentarily to fetch weather data and is not stored or maintained by us. Security Measures: We implement reasonable security measures to protect the information collected by the Application from unauthorized access, disclosure, or misuse. However, please understand that no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is entirely secure, and we cannot guarantee absolute security. Your Consent: By using our Weather Application, you consent to the terms outlined in this Privacy Policy. Updates to the Privacy Policy: We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes will be reflected in the</string>
</resources>